English-language manuscript verse in the Houghton Library, circa 1000-1820: First-line index.
English-language manuscript verse in the Houghton Library circa 1000-1820,
There coffee-man, vintner, the victualler and brewer (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 84v
There constant show'rs of hail and rains do flow (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 87v
There doth beauty dwell There most conspicuous in outward shape (incomplete) MS Keats 3.13, ii, 122v
There dwelt twa sisters in a bower (incomplete) MS Eng 1497, ii, 42v; MS Am 2349, xxi, 78
There groweth all the malmsey (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 4
There grows a bonny briar bush in our kailyard MS Eng 1497, ii, 39
There he sits by a brook, watching a quill MS Eng 1490, 82
There is a charm in footing slow across a silent plain MS Keats 2.19, 1
There is a child born to our blessing shall bring MS Eng 1507, Christmas carrols, 1767, 3; MS Eng 1507, Christmas carrols, [ca. 1777], 18
There is a joy in footing slow across a silent plain MS Keats 3.2, 213; MS Keats 1.34
There is a land of vast delight MS Eng 862, 10
There is a moment when the mind MS Thr 198, folder 79
There is a monarch in an isle say some MS Eng 636F, 149
There is a mystic thread of life MS Eng 1484, 44
There is a pleasure in the pathless woods (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 21
There is a stane in yon water (incomplete) MS Eng 1471, i, 110
There is a talk in Glasgow town MS Eng 862, 103; MS Eng 862.1, 6
There is a word of letters three MS Eng 569.67, 80
There is a word of plural number MS Eng 569.67, 84
There is a youth fit for the nones MS Eng 686, 75
There is no doubt that there exists voices in dreams (incomplete) MS Keats 3.13, ii, 20
There is no man so lewd of life MS Eng 1503 (3), ii, 193
There is no other medicine against love MS Keats 2.15.1, 13
There is no peace but in a virtuous life (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 55
There is no rain, no sleet, no snow (incomplete) MS Eng 1503 (3), vol. ii, p. 115 tipped in
There is no tree that grow MS Eng 1503 (3), vol. iii, p. 13
There is not a tailor in all London town MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 63
There is one word of letters three MS Eng 569.67, 78
There is three things that will make a man lean MS Eng 1497, ii, 49
There leeft a May an' a well far'd May MS Eng 1470, 101
There leeved a wee man at the fit o' yon hill MS Eng 1470, 76
There likewise mote be seen on every side MS Eng 611, i, 126
There liv'd a gentleman, possest MS Eng 612, ii, 140
There liv'd a lad in Singerumshire MS Eng 1491 (3), 22
There liv'd a lady in Barnesdale MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 220
There liv'd a lady in Edinburgh city MS Eng 862, 127
There liv'd a laird down into Fife (incomplete) MS Eng 1486 (2), 54
There liv'd a lass in Auster town MS Eng 1491 (3), 7v
There liv'd a man tho' really good MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 220v
There liv'd, as authors tell, in days of yore (incomplete) MS Eng 616, i, 8
There lived a carl in Kelly burn braes MS Eng 1497, ii, 171v
There lived a husbandman near the sea strand MS Eng 1470, 34
There lived a king in southern land MS Eng 1497, ii, 1
There lived a knight in Jesuitmont MS Eng 1470, 69
There lived a lady in the south MS Eng 1497, i, 4v
There lived a lass into yon bank MS Eng 1470, 17
There lived a lord in the West Country MS Eng 1470, 206
There lived a Lord into the South (incomplete) MS Eng 862, 225
There lived a man in fair Scotland MS Eng 1471, v, 135
There lived a man in the North Countree (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, 186
There lived a man in the Northwest land MS Am 2349, xxvi, 708; MS Eng 1444, 25v and 42
There lived a man into the west MS Eng 1470, 8v
There lived a man on Noranside MS Eng 1504, 6
There lived farmer in the North MS Eng 1444, 35
There lived three sisters in a bow'r MS Eng 1471, ii, 27
There lives a fair maid near hard by MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 172
There lives a frog in yonder well MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 75v
There lives a king in southern land MS Eng 1470, 158
There lives a lady in Farnesdale MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 198v
There lives a lady in London MS Eng 1471, v, 56; MS Eng 1471, vii, 14
There lives a lass just at the cross MS Eng 1470, 68; MS Eng 1470, 13
There lives a man in our gate end MS Eng 1497, ii, 141
There lives a sauter in Millden MS Eng 1471, v, 52
There lives a young man in this town MS Eng 1471, v, 70v
There lives a young man near hard by MS Eng 1471, v, 14v
There lives within the very flame of love (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2 (twice)
There long were we neglected; and we bore P.S. (incomplete) MS Eng 327, "To Miss Taylor Apr. 9, 1801"; MS Eng 327(68)
There sat the gentle savage of the wild (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 99
There souls of men are bought and sold MS Eng 1167, 54
There spread round Murray all your blooming loves (incomplete) MS Eng 731, folder 275, 10
There stands a knicht at the tap o' yon hill MS Eng 1471, vii, 83
There stands the messenger of truththere stands (incomplete) MS Keats 3.13, ii, 4v
There surrounds us again, as her world MS Am 1428 (168)
There taught to work, to dance, to sing and play (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 88
There the hoarse screech-owl, that in dead of night MS Eng 611, i, 103
There the large olive rains its amber store (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 87
Theretrace where tranquil o'er his track of trail (incomplete) MS Eng 265.1, folder 15
There war three bonnie boys playing at the ba' MS Eng 1471, i, 20
There was a battle in the North MS Eng 1471, v, 69v; MS Eng 1470, 42; MS Eng 1470, 119 and 129 and 221
There was a bonny young lassie MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 89v
There was a bridal in our town MS Eng 1491 (3), 45v
There was a bridal in this town MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 72v; MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 89v
There was a British merchant MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 138
There was a certain usurer, he had a pretty niece MS Eng 1038.1, 40
There was a Duke and he dwelt in York MS Eng 862, 233
There was a duke's daughter MS Eng 1491 (3), 13v
There was a farmer's daughter MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 234
There was a fine widow! a fine one indeed MS Eng 834, folder 60
There was a froggie lived in a well MS Eng 1506, 11
There was a gallant ship MS Eng 862.1, loose leaf at end
There was a Gip came o'er the land MS Am 2349, xxvii, 819
There was a gourd or Melion long ago MS Eng 247.5, 40
There was a haggis in Dunbar MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 160v; MS Eng 1491 (3), 21; MS Eng 1497, ii, 141v
There was a handsome astrologer MS Eng 1471, v, 33v
There was a happy omen in the case MS Eng 569.64, 59
There was a jolly beggar (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, in envelope fixed to back cover
There was a jolly beggar, and a begging he had been (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxix, 1029
There was a jolly beggar, in begging well aquaint MS Eng 512, 30; MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 118
There was a jolly harper man MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 25
There was a jolly miller once MS Eng 1038.1, 71v
There was a jovial beggar, with a wooden leg MS Eng 512, 30v
There was a jovial beggar-man MS Am 2349, xxix, 1031
There was a jury sat at Perth MS Eng 1497, ii, 44v
There was a king and a curious king MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 83v
There was a knicht and a lady bricht MS Eng 1471, i, 119
There was a knight, and a gallant knight was he MS Eng 1498, 40
There was a knight as Jerryman (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxviii, 950
There was a knight in a summer's night was riding o'er the lee Diddle MS Eng 1486 (2), 49
There was a knight in Jesuit MS Eng 1497, ii, 32; MS Am 2349, xxviii, 947 and 948
There was a knight kept sheep up in yon glen MS Eng 1497, ii, 117; MS Am 2349, xxiv, 460
There was a knight o' the Jesuit (incomplete) MS Eng 862, 242v
There was a knight on the head o' yon hill MS Am 2349, xxi, 8
There was a lady fair MS Am 2349, ii, 31; MS Eng 1471, iii, 75; MS Eng 1471, v, 99v
There was a lady fair, and e'en a lady of birth and fame MS Eng 1498, 45v
There was a lady fair and gay MS Am 2349, xxiii, 364
There was a lady fair, fair MS Eng 1471, v, 160
There was a lady gay MS Eng 1491 (3), 26
There was a lady's daughter MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 152
There was a lady of the North Country MS Am 2349, xxi, 3
There was a laird of fair Scotland MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 212
There was a lame beggar and he had a wooden leg MS Eng 1471 v, 62v
There was a lass in the North Countrie (incomplete) MS Am 2349, v, p. 71; MS Am 2349, xxiv, 418; MS Eng 1470, 65; MS Eng 862.1, loose leaf at end
There was a little plot of level ground MS Eng 1316, 7
There was a little wee Bridlee MS Eng 1471 v, 51v
There was a little wifeikie MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 214
There was a little woman, as I've heard tell MS Eng 1038.1, 70
There was a lord in this country MS Eng 1471 v, 77
There was a lord lived in the East MS Am 2349, xxviii, 965
There was a lowering in the eastern sky MS Eng 1094, 11
There was a man lived in the West (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxi, 82 and 84; MS Am 2349, xxix, 1027
There was a man of Adam's race MS Am 1177, 13v
There was a man was full of wit MS Eng 703, 69
There was a may, a maiden sae gae MS Eng 1471 i, 74
There was a may and a well-far'd may MS Eng 1497, i, 182v
There was a mousie in a mill MS Eng 1470, 61
There was a mousie in the mill MS Eng 1471 iii, 7
There was a painter whom I cannot name MS Eng 247.5, 34
There was a paperhanger once, who lived in the Strand, sirs MS Eng 692, 36
There was a poor silly harper man MS Eng 1470, 32
There was a power in this sweet place *EC8. Sh445. 929n, 3v
There was a Presbyterian's cat MS Eng 1497, ii, 65v
There was a proud pedlar, a fine pedlar MS Am 2349, xxv, 590
There was a sauter, and they ca'd him Gill MS Eng 1471 v, 45v
There was a shepherd's boy MS Am 2349, xxiv, 459
There was a shepherd's daughter MS Eng 862, 135; MS Am 2349, xxiv, 442 and 447; MS Eng 1471 v, 15v
There was a shepherd's daughter, kept hogs upo' yon hill MS Eng 1470, 168
There was a shepherd's dochter MS Eng 1471 v, 131; MS Eng 1471 vii, 32 and 36
There was a ship, a ship of fame MS Eng 1471 v, 142v
There was a ship of the North Countrie (incomplete) MS Am 2349, v, p. 86; MS Eng 1470, in envelope fixed to back cover; MS Eng 862.1,loose leaf at end
There was a sauter they ca'd Gill MS Eng 1471 vii, 138
There was a squire lived in Edinborough town MS Am 2349, xxvii, 881
There was a tailor at a time MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 130v
There was a tailor at the Newck o' Clachan's fauld MS Eng 1471 vii, 125
There was a time, before the times of story MS Eng 36, 3
There was a troop of Irish dragoons MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 142v
There was a troop of soldiers brave MS Am 2349, ii, p. 186
There was a wealthy farmer MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 135v; MS Am 2349, xxix, 1030
There was a wee bit wedding (incomplete) MS Eng 1506, 7
There was a wee bit wifeikie (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxvi, 715
There was a wee bit wifeikie was comin' frae the fair MS Eng 1497, i, 31v
There was a widow in Westmoreland MS Am 2349, ii, p. 211
There was a wife and she had nae bairns MS Eng 1497, ii, 123
There was a youth, and a well-beloved youth MS Am 2349, xxiv, 420 and 421 and 422
There was also a Nonne, a prioresse (incomplete) MS Typ 560, 13v
There was an ancient ship, and an ancient ship was she (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxix, 1041
There was an auld farmer, my grandfather kenn'd him MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 222
There was an auld man stood on a stane MS Eng 1504, 8
There was an auld priest's wife MS Eng 1491 (3), 16v
There was an auld woman tossed up in a blanket MS Eng 1497, ii, 165v
There was an old astrologer MS Eng 1491 (3), 40v
There was an old lad rid on an old pad MS Eng 628, 165
There was an old man had a house MS Eng 895, 98v
There was an old woman lived under a hill MS Eng 569.67, 32
There was an old woman who lived at Dundee MS Eng 742, item 39, 2v
There was at court a lady of late MS Eng 686, 34
There was four and twenty ladies MS Am 2349, xxiii, 371
There was Ixion turned on a wheel MS Eng 584, 94v
There was Johnson and Jackson as I have heard them say (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxi, 83
There was many a braw noble come to our king's ha' MS Eng 1504, 4v
There was no death nor worldly joy MS Eng 1503 (3), vol. iii, p. 6
There was once a lady in the north muir dwelt MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 215
There was once a May, an' she lo' 'ed nae men MS Eng 1486 (3), 29
There was seven gipsies all in a row MS Am 2349, xxvii, 828
There was seven gypsies all in a gang MS Am 2349, xxvii, 818 and 827
There was sleeping Sim of the Lamb Hill MS Eng 862, 147
There was such a man as King William, there was MS Am 2349, xxiii, 340
There was three ladies played at the ba' MS Am 2349, xxi, 87; MS Eng 1470, 60; MS Eng 1486 (4), 16 and 75
There was three ladies playing at the ba' MS Eng 1497, ii, 13v
There was three ravens in a tree (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxii, 150
There was twa sisters in a bour (incomplete) MS Am 2349, v, p. 54; MS Eng 1486 (1), 55
There was twa sisters in a bow'r, Edinburgh, Edinburgh MS Eng 1486 (2), 46
There was twa sisters liv'd in a bouir (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, 33v
There was two birds sat on a stone MS Eng 768 (vol. 1), 45v
There was two brothers in the navy MS Eng 1471 vi, 24
There was two notorious thieves MS Eng 895, 15
There waur aucht an' forty nobles MS Eng 1444, 17
There waur three ladies in a ha' MS Eng 1444, 11v
There was a couple and they were poor MS Eng 1471 v, 36v
There were a knight and a lady bright MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 85; MS Am 2349, xxiv, 461
There were a troop of soldiers brave MS Eng 1470, 135
There were five ladies lived in a bower MS Eng 1471 i, 107
There were four and twenty gentlemen MS Eng 1471 i, 151
There were four-an'-twenty soldiers bold MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 92v
There were seven gypsies all in a row (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxvii, 829
There were seven gypsies on a day MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 27 and p. 33
There were seven Oys into Milnhole (incomplete) MS Am 2349, ii, p. 232
There were three ladies in a ha' MS Eng 1444, 41
There were three ladies playing at the ba' MS Eng 1497, ii, 10; MS Am 2349, v, p. 54; MS Am 2349, xxi, 83
There were three lads in our town MS Eng 1491 (3), 68
There were three lords drinking at the wine (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, 93; MS Eng 862.1, loose leaf at end
There were three ravens sat on a tree MS Am 2349, xxii, 148; MS Eng 1470, 224
There were three sisters playing ball (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 27 and 32
There were twa brothers in the east MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 36
There were twa sisters in a bour (incomplete) MS Am 2349, v, p. 177; MS Eng 1470, 48
There were twa sisters lived in a bower MS Eng 1471 v, 217
There were twa sisters sat in a bower MS Eng 1470, 105
There were two brothers in the North MS Am 2349, xxiii, 255
There were two sisters in a bower MS Am 2349, xxi, 85
Therefore with thee triumpheth there MS Eng 966.4, 86v
Therefore your halls, your ancient colleges MS Eng 952.1, 1v
There's a language that's mute, there's a silence that speaks MS Keats 3.13, i, 57
There's a rose in my apron to Sandy, O MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 132v
There's buckies i' bog, theres gairies i' glen (incomplete) MS Eng 1444, 34v
There's fifty young nobles rides up the king's hall MS Eng 1470, 156
There's five o' them with meal and malt (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, 54
There's Johnie o' the busky glen (incomplete) MS Eng 1471 vii, 127
There's kames o' hinney 'tween my luve's lip MS Eng 1497, i, 12v
There's lads to baith our lasses yet MS Eng 1504, 11
There's many a ane in Methorn been MS Eng 1471 vi, 26
There's many a lassie in this town (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, 93
There's many like to this old man MS Eng 247.5, 41v
There's mirth again among the boughs MS Eng 1505, 18
There's my thumb. I'll ne'er beguile you MS Eng 512, 40; MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 120
There's nae bed that I like, like one amang the straw MS Eng 1471 v, 46
There's news is gaen in the kitchen (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxvi, 715 and 716
There's no disturbance in the heavens above MS Eng 584, 24
There's no harm in sound cunts nor in arseholes MS Eng 636F, 31v
There's no jesting with edge tools (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
There's no making a whistle of a pig's tale MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
There's no more credit to be given to th' face (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 2v
There's no perfection That you are mistress of, but musters up (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 35v
There's no skill (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
There's no skill In being good; but in not being thought ill (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
There's no such thing as constancy in nature (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 5
There's not a breath Will mingle kindly with the meadow air (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 57
There's nothing in the world which I can name MS Eng 584, 79
There's nothing in this world, like you I prize (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 22v
There's nought but willing, waking love that can (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 65v
There's nought, no doubt, so much the spirit calms (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 36
There's Queensberry, Seafield, and Marr MS Eng 1497, ii, 96
There's some say that we wan MS Eng 1497, i, 22v
There's Sunderland the Tory MS Eng 633, 27v
There's three white hens in the green, Madam MS Eng 1497, ii, 55v
There's twice as much music in beating the tabor (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2 (twice)
Thersites only clamored in the throng (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 60
Thes fittnes grounded on parfit charite (incomplete) MS Eng 1482, Harl 2255, 115
These and a thousand fears my soul possess (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 74
These are the jewels that do store heaven's treasure MS Eng 702, 14v
These are the reasons that are given (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 46
These are the vestry that expends (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 80v
These ballads have been long out of repair MS Eng 1501, 2
These factions amongst great men, they are like (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 5v
These fluttering fops imagine they can wind MS Thr 39, 11v
These gates he shut so wonderly well (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxiv, 486
These gross, il-shuffled lots from heaven are sent (incomplete) MS Eng 1312, 47v
These heaps of stones, these old walls which ye see MS Eng 266, 63
These lines had kissed their hands October last MS Eng 624, 35
These lines, put in order, wrote down by a pen MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 230v
These men of war As I have heard, know not to court a lady (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 32v
These, my lord, assembled at the bar (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 68v
These scatterand Scots MS Eng 766, 154
These seven days I last did pass MS Eng 645, 65
These signs the world's combustion shall forerun (incomplete) MS Eng 631, 2
These silent features with his silence sign'd (incomplete) MS Eng 631, 15
These simple lines flowed with a doubling hope (incomplete) MS Eng 327 (4), p. 3
These sixty years I've led my life MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 216v; MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 182
These statesmen nothing woo but gold and power (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 98
These striking pleasing beams Franc Beaumont threw MS Eng 228, 7v
These suff'rings, madam, I should count but light (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 22
These threads enjoy a double grace MS Eng 686, 61v
These veins and nature's net MS Eng 686, 61
These verses herewith now I do begin MS Eng 623
These walls were rais'd by men who did a deed (incomplete) MS Eng 505
Thespis, the first professor of our arts MS Eng 584, 39
They are at our gates, my heart! Affrights and horrors (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 36
They are fair sisterstho' their features be MS Eng 630, 37
They are the wise, not only who provide MS Eng 614, 101
They asked him and speired him (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxvii, 882
They by th'alluring odor drawn, in haste (incomplete) MS Eng 731, folder 143
They ca' me Nelly Douglas 'bout the house (incomplete) MS Eng 1444, 34v
They ca' my faither windy Tom MS Eng 1506, 10
They call thee nightingale, fair maid MS Am 2001 (17), 1
They called for tea and chocolate (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 93
They crave for fops, as girls green fruit devour (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 134
They hardly rise unto renown (incomplete) MS Eng 631, 5v
They have one waggery the top o' th' rest (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 90v
They jangle, and their maxims disagree (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 138v
They preached and prayed by inward light (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 40
They rally'd next Vanessa's dress (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 93v
They say that I am silent and my silence they condemn MS Eng 936 (v.1), 97
They say that we tailors are Things that lay one another, and our geese (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2 (twice)
They scorn'd to truck, for base unmanly arts (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 107
They seemed so calm, and with their age so brave (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
They seemed so calm, and with their life so brave (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
They sent him away to a far country (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 31
They set me in a chair of state (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxv, 615
They sit 'em down; I mean in pews (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 41
They still pursued: as when two skillful hounds (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 110
They talk of three goddesses in Ida vales MS Eng 629, 21v
They thought to lie in Methven kirkyard MS Eng 1470, 8v
They were saddled a', they wer bridled a' MS Eng 1497, ii, 39v
They who advent'rous plow the wat'ry ways (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 113v
They who must traffic jewels, but by glance MS Eng 623
They who the longest lease enjoy (incomplete) MS Eng 676F, 31
They've beat us now: but all my trust is MS Thr 198, folder 40
Th'increase of Jacob's flock is grown past number MS Typ 49, 9
Thine, on Cantium's hills, The flow'ry hop, whose tendrils climbing round (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 60v
Th'infernal orator now paused a space (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 65
Things both of danger and of profit fear MS Eng 614, 100v
Things left thus to the sleep-god's care (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 44
Th'inhospitable land, left desolate (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 102v
Think not cause men flattering say MS Eng 686, 90
Think not of it, sweet one, so MS Keats 3.2, 16; MS Keats 3.1, 12v; MS Keats 4.4.4, 1
Think not, sweet love, that I'll reveal MS Eng 686, 51
Think on the noble exploits of his life (incomplete) MS Keats 3.13, ii, 19v
Think you all treasure Hid in the bowels of the earth, or shipwreck'd (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 35
Think'st thou, 'cause rich, thou stand'st on higher ground MS Eng 614, 100v
Th'insulting fair (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 133v
This all?yet is wonderful-exceeding (incomplete) MS Keats 3.2, 238
This among man's general disease MS Eng 614, 97
This anguish will be wearied down, I know (incomplete) MS Keats 3.13, ii, 20
This bold relief a finished work MS Eng 569.63, 3
This book again the law of God repeats MS Typ 49, 20
This book by any yet unread MS Am 1007, 26; MS Am 1007.1, 22
This book, thy album, passively receives Ms Am 1034, 55
This book was scratched and blurred within (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 44
This cap that so stately appears MS Eng 870, folder 64C
This commoner has worth and parts MS Eng 768 (vol. 1), 19
This Cyclops, as historians tell us (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 40
This day a festival we keep MS Eng 834, folder 61
This day Dame Nature seem'd in love MS Eng 1490, 79v; MS Eng 886, 1
This day time winds th'exhausted chain Autograph file, B: Robert Burns, 1
This day your empire fate secures MS Eng 1035, 9
This diet still a shrew provides MS Eng 247.5, 52
This doth a wretched dearth of wit betray (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 55
This double dower no doubt will turn her brain (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 139
This evening late, by then the chewing flocks (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 132v
This face observe, discerning fair MS Eng 1038.1, 17v
This fault was hers, which 'twere in vain to hide MS Eng 612, ii, 89
This fav'rite maxim modern atheists boast (incomplete) MS Eng 614, 27v
This fifth of November MS Eng 645, 75
This figure, lo, Augustus did devise MS Typ 14, 55v
This form engraven was in noble Pompey's ring MS Typ 14, 90v
This fragrant emblem of her curious thought MS Eng 613, 38v
This gentle ev'ning let the sun descend (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 112
This girdle doth the waist embrace MS Eng 686, 61v
This greatens, fills, immortalizes all (incomplete) MS Eng 680, 60v
This happy day two lights are seen MS Eng 631, 66
This iron age, so fraudulent and bold MS Eng 631, 73